<resources>
    <string name="app_name">JudaismProject</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--About-->
    <string name="content">My project focuses on Jewish representation in Japanese media. I analyzed Tezuka Osamu\'s manga "Message to Adolf". The manga focuses on World War II in Japan. It is based off the rumors that Hitler
    had Jewish ancestry. The manga focuses on three people named Adolf. The first is Adolf Hitler, the second is Adolf Kaufmann (Japanese/German), and Adolf Kamil (Jewish).</string>
    <string name="findings">In the manga, Jews are portrayed as strong, confident, trustworthy and moral. Tezuka highlights Jews and their suffering during the Holocaust. But oddly, I also found that
    Japan depicted themselves as victims alongside the Jews.</string>
    <string name="argument">Japan uses Jews to rewrite their militant history.</string>
    <string name="app">This app was made for a Judaism through Film class at Mills College in Spring 2018. It contains three other sections. The manga section for a preview of the manga, a quiz for learning about the topic, and the bibliography.</string>


    <!--Bibliography strings-->
    <string name="osamu">Osamu, Tezuka. Adorufu ni Tsugu. Tokyo: Bungeishunjū, 1983-1985. </string>
    <string name="goodman">Goodman, David G. and Masanori Miyazawa. Jews in the Japanese Mind: The History and Uses of a Cultural Stereotype (Studies of Modern Japan) (Lanham: Lexington Books, 2000), 135-182.</string>
    <string name="ito">Ito, Kinko. “A History of Manga in the Context of Japanese Culture and Society.” Journal of Popular Culture 38, no.3 (2005): 456-475.</string>
    <string name="kowner">Kowner, Rotem. “On Ignorance, Respect, and Suspicion: Current Japanese Attitudes towards Jews”, Analysis of Current Trends in Antisemitism, no.11 (1997), http://www.academia.edu/12556038/On_Ignorance_Respect_and_Suspicion_Current_Japanese_Attitudes_towards_Jews.</string>
    <string name="shimazu">Shimazu, Naoko. "Popular Representations of the Past: The Case of Postwar Japan." Journal of Contemporary History 38, no. 1 (2003): 101-16.</string>
    <string name="taijima">Tajima, Atsushi, and Michael Thornton. "Strategic solidarity: Japanese imaginings of Blacks and race in popular media." Inter-Asia Cultural Studies 13, no. 3 (September 2012): 345-364. Academic Search Complete, EBSCOhost (accessed March 7, 2018).</string>
    <string name="manga">Manga</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="bibliography">Bibliography</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>

</resources>
